<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Colombia Turistica: Medellin</string>
    <string name="ComCh">Chinese Food</string>
    <string name="ComCol">Colombian Food</string>
    <string name="ComInV">Varied International Food</string>
    <string name="ComIta" >Italian Food</string>
    <string name="ComRap" >Fast Food</string>
    <string name="DesAR" >The typical Colombian food has that homemade taste infected with much love and sacrifice, as it began zeros, were just what I had wanted to work and make this small space a haven for customers and comenzales</string>
    <string name="DesAng" >Brangus-Brangus is an international restaurant specializing in meat, fish, and seafood paella. We aim to offer a friendly and quiet, accompanied by drinks and high quality meals time.</string>
    <string name="DesCD" >For lovers of American cuisine, opens in Envigado in the capital of Antioquia Classic Diner, a place where you can enjoy the best dishes of this cuisine but served gourmet type. Its decor evokes the best American classic bars with décor in the style of the 50 providing a fun and comfortable environment</string>
    <string name="DesCW" >An art that transforms the food in love and joy. Nourishes the soul and body, captivates palates and conquer hearts.</string>
    <string name="DesCielo" >In El Cielo, we create unique dining experiences that emphasize the sensory side, offering a tasting menu inspired not only in Colombian ancestral roots, but in neuroscience studies on the stimulation of the senses through food, so we provide food for the body... and soul</string>
    <string name="DesCine" >In Medellin are theaters throughout the city, there are 3 main companies that are spread over all comercilaes centers of the city, can here find the link to the page of each company to encuntres the nearest cinema, movies in theaters and funcones:</string>
    <string name="DesCineCol" >It is the leading film company in Medellin, with five theaters scattered throughout the city, to see her in Communications, billboard and functions, go to http //: www.cinecolombia.com</string>
    <string name="DesComRap" >As in any self-respecting city are getting fast food of all kinds, large miltinacionales as McDonalds, Burger King, Subway, KFC, etc; tri-fold found in almost every mall in the city alunos Places, the calsicos carts fast food you will find in most corners of the pink areas and neighborhoods of the city loa.</string>
    <string name="DesCuz" >Cuzco is a restaurant that continues the boom of Peruvian food in the world, is that this country is full of exoticism and wisdom as far as food is concerned.</string>
    <string name="DesIlFo" >With our attention, fair prices, generous portions, welcoming environments and excellent quality in our products quality, we hope to always provide the best casual dining, plus an excellent service to be the perfect combination to meet the needs of our customers.</string>
    <string name="DesInCh" >The quality of our product and service excellence, complemented by the majestic architecture and sieño restaurant, that breaks the landscape and invites you to enjoy an unforgettable expereince</string>
    <string name="DesMed2" >Welcome to a city that inspires, flowers and transforms everyday</string>
    <string name="DesMon" >Mondongos is a leader in the gastronomic sector and Antiochian typical kitchen tradition, with presence at national and international level</string>
    <string name="DesMuse" >In Medellin You can find a lot of museums with different themes and large parks for recreation, the most representative museum of the city is the Museum of Antioquia, located in the center of town surrounded by the majestic park Botero, where exhibited outdoors a large number of sculptures of the famous paisa sculptor Fernando Botero, you can also find others like the Museum of Modern Art and Museum on Located Castle in the district the Town, also find the Mueso Water Located in the Administrative area city, close to park of Lights, and Barefoot park that adorn the Intelligent Building, home to one of the largest companies in the country, EPM.</string>
    <string name="DesPaEx" >From the crisp broccoli we use in our Chicken Shiitake to the delicious red peppers Beef our Beijing, we like to make sure we always offer flavor and quality of our dishes.</string>
    <string name="DesParBiblio" >The city shows its cultural and educational transformation in the library parks, spaces that combine knowledge so surprising amenities. The architectural features of the library parks, generous designs, furniture and public spaces, changed for the better the cityscape, and daily life, not only of the inhabitants of the areas where they are built, but the entire city.</string>
    <string name="DesParm" >This restaurant craft tradition lives of good food, the toast of a good wine and a delicious meal. We are committed to your health, so all of our products are handmade with fresh and natural ingredients.</string>
    <string name="DesPas" >Artisan Pasta of the highest quality, to develop the best Italian food in town, Recomendadismo for lovers of pasta and Italian food</string>
    <string name="DesPeMi" >PERU MIX is the first chain style "fast-food" Peruvian food in Medellin and Colombia. Here you can enjoy the best of the Peruvian food and gourmet express, in a fun casual atmosphere, young, economic and funny.</string>
    <string name="DesProc" >It is another positioned company in the city of Medellin with three theaters in this city, and 3 other theaters scattered in neighboring municipalities that form the Medellin Metropolitan Area, for its location, billboard and functions entering http //: www. procinal.com</string>
    <string name="DesPtoIn" >It is a restaurant that offers the best of the Peruvian food where you can find dishes from a traditional Peruvian Ceviche to our delicious lomo saltado and to sweeten their palates must prove the Lima Sigh, ancestral sweet Limeña pastries, everything always accompanied a delicious Pisco Sour signature drink of Peru.</string>
    <string name="DesRan" >The flavor of our dishes retains the traditional recipes of her grandmother, flavors that are the result of the mixture of ingredients that always have the best quality products ... are selected very carefully every day.</string>
    <string name="DesResMed" >Such restaurants are the most abundant in the city, we will give examples variaos depending on the type of food, so you can enjoy them all as they are of very good quality and good prices.</string>
    <string name="DesRestau" >Medellín es una ciudad donde puedes encontrar todo tipo de restaurantes o lugares para comer, desde el carrito de comida rapidas en cada esquina de las zonas rosas y barrios, hasta Restaurantes Reconocidos internacionalmente como El Cielo, que se encuentra en el ranking de los mejores 49 del Mundo; asi tambien puedes econtrar una variadad infinita de precios, desde lo 5000 pesos hasta los 300000, este dependera del sector, comida y lugar elegido, asi pues te prentaremos algunos de los mas famosos entre los Paisas, ya que nombrarlos todos seria Imposible; esperamos disfrutes de una buena comida y que se acomode a tus necesidades:</string>
    <string name="DesRoyal" >Film company has 3 theaters in the city, you can see your location, billboard and functions at http //: www.royal-films.com</string>
    <string name="DesRutan" >The Route N complex is a sector north of the city of Medellin where you can find plenty of places to visit, where you will be surprised with grandiose structures, you learn with incredible theme park and have fun in extreme games and family. This complex is intended to be the center of the Innovation City, since there is the University of Antioquia, one of the most prestigious universities in the city and the country, the research center of the University of Antioquia (SIU) The majestic building Route, building where a lot of companies dedicated to the research, including HP. Later you will find the extraordinary Park of Desires, a design inspired by the research of the stars Park, there you will find the planetarium of the city, where you can enjoy its beautiful projections, about far more meters will find the Parque Explora A large theme park focused on the areas of science such as physics, biology, chemistry, etc. And find the majestic city aquarium, the largest in Colombia and one of the largest in Latin America, next to this you will find the beautiful Botanical Gardens of Medellin, great space of flora and fauna, with majestic Orquideorama where You can enjoy the variety of orchids the national flower of Colombia. And if you are looking for fun across the park scans can find North Park, the park of extreme games in town where you will find a lot of family to have fun all afternoon extreme rides and you can guide a little the map shown above and enjoy this beautiful city.</string>
    <string name="DesTM" >It is one of the most important theaters in large format of the city, situated near Plaza Mayor, which is the quintessential Event Center City.</string>
    <string name="DesTeatAD" >Barefoot Eagle headquarters in the traditional neighborhood of Medellin Prado is a beautiful mansion, for its architectural value and ongoing programming has become urban, cultural and tourist reference must for residents and visitors to the city. There Theater Prado Museum, a building has terraces, halls and galleries where art activities, academic and business meetings, seminars, audiovisual works are performed, among others</string>
    <string name="DesTeatros" >In Medellin you find great theaters, medium and small format, which adorn the city with quality shows and events, imbued with great creativity and excellent organization. Its programming is constant throughout the year, offering a space for healthy recreation for visitors, making all who share a taste for the theatrical culture can enjoy each of the events held there, and entertainment infecting their lives , other cultures, many artistic sensibilities and feelings. You can disfutarlos in all price ranges, from buying a ticket in the big theaters gratiuta entrance to a voluntary collaboration.</string>
    <string name="ResMed" >Restaurants Middle Class</string>
    <string name="ResPeru" >Peruvian Food</string>
    <string name="ResPtoIn" >Restaurant Puerto Inca</string>
    <string name="ResTom" >Restaurant Tony Romas</string>
    <string name="Rest" >Restaurants</string>
    <string name="RestLujo" >Restaurants First Class</string>
    <string name="Rumba1" >Being the second largest city in Colombia, with the reputation of hosting the country is most beautiful people, enjoy the nightlife and "La Fiesta Paisa" is something to do when visiting this vibrant city.</string>
    <string name="Sitos" >Tourist sites</string>
    <string name="TaetPeT" >The continuous research, development and teaching has made small theater one of the most solid and representative groups of the Colombian stage movement. Their offices and theaters are in a house of Republican architecture located in the center of the city (Córdoba x Beach). For its human resources and physical infrastructure small theater was declared heritage.</string>
    <string name="TeatMetr" >Theatre Metropolitano</string>
    <string name="TeatPT" >Theatre Pablo Tobon Uribe</string>
    <string name="TeatUM" >Theatre Univesity of Medellin</string>
    <string name="TeatrAD" >Theatre Aguila Descalza</string>
    <string name="TeatrPo" >Theatre El Poblado</string>
    <string name="Teatro" >Theatre</string>
    <string name="TeatrosPF" >Small theaters Format</string>
    <string name="TetrMF" >Medium-format theaters</string>
    <string name="barrio" >For lovers of reggaeton (we are sure there are several!) We recommend going to the Barrio Colombia (near the subway station Industrial) where there are many bars and a disco called Prisma.</string>
    <string name="la33" >But if you are looking for a more local experience, we recommend venturing to the Calle 33 (only weekends) or around the schools where you will find many cheap bars and good atmosphere.</string>
    <string name="lleras" >Parque Lleras in El Poblado, is an area of bars, restaurants and clubs like The Blue, B-Lounge or Babylon. There are also several places on a stretch of the Carrera 38 in Las Palmas, near the town, including the strange and attractive Sweet Jesus Mine. In addition, there are also many hostels so travelers can find different ways to enjoy different options during your visit. However, if you really want to enjoy the nightlife in Medellin, there are many more options available in the city.</string>
    <string name="rumbaC" >For something more chic, visit the Golden Mile and La Strada; a kind of mall where you will find clubs, bars and restaurants but better yet, the most impressive concentration of beautiful women you have seen and will see in a lifetime ... A similar atmosphere will find two minute walk in RioSur that, on the seventh floor, home to many discos and Attic and Kukaramakura.</string>
    <string name="teatGF" >Large Format Theatres :</string>
    <string name="DesTom">Tony Romas is a restaurant chain known worldwide for its BBQ ribs, a practice typical of the kitchen that will hadado around the world, is located on the top floor of the Hotel Dann Carlton Medellin is the only gourmet stop rotating 360 in the city of Medellin.</string>
    <string name="MusPar">Major museums and parks</string>
</resources>